Contact

8685086183 (Mobile) vanshjatana99@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vansh-jatana (LinkedIn)

www.theaimonk.com/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Data Analysis

Machine Learning

Data Science

Certifications

Information Security and Quality Assurance

Office 365 Development

Practical PHP

Deep Learning

Data Visualization

Honors-Awards

Honour Code for Trainers

AIR 5

SQL gold level badge

IBM 20 badges holder

Kaggle Grandmaster

Publications

Classifying Metastatic Cancer Lymph Node Histopathology Using Cross Validation on Convolutional Neural Networks

How To Choose ML Algorithm

SEMANTIC ANALYSIS OF COVID-19 RESEARCH PAPERS

Machine Learning in Action

Hyperparameter Tuning

Vansh Jatana

Data Scientist at Pattern ai Chennai

Summary

Vansh Jatana is a Data scientist, presently enrolled in an undergraduate program Computer Science major at SRM Institute of Science and Technology, India. He is amongst the top 15 in the world as Kaggle's Notebook Grandmaster. As an author at O'Reilly and Analytics Vidhya, Vansh has published articles on the plethora of data science topics. He is also recognized by NASA and worked as an intern in several multinational companies. His areas of interest are machine learning, natural language processing, and artificial intelligence. He love spending his free time playing table-tennis, designing posters and watching movies.

Experience

Pattern ai
Data Scientist
March 2020 - Present (6 months)
United States

BlueThinq
Data Scientist
July 2020 - Present (2 months)
London, England, United Kingdom

Analytics Vidhya Technical Writer May 2020 - Present (4 months)

Quantium
Data Analyst
June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months)
Virtual

Data preparation and customer analytics

Experimentation and uplift testing

Analytics and commercial application

ANZ

Data Analyst May 2020 - June 2020 (2 months)

Virtual

Exploratory Data Analysis-Segment the dataset and draw unique insights, including visualisation of the transaction volume and assessing the effect of any outliers.

Predictive Analytics-Explore correlations between customer attributes, build a regression and a decision-tree prediction model based on your findings.

Microsoft MBA Virtual Internship May 2020 - June 2020 (2 months) Virtual

- 1. Campus to Corporate: Business Foundation Skills
- 2. Work Ready Skills
- 3. Technical GTM skills

All About IT
Data Scientist
January 2020 - April 2020 (4 months)
Chennai Area, India

Self-employed
Data Scientist
August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

NACHI Data Analyst May 2019 - July 2019 (3 months) Gurgaon, Haryana, India

Coordinated statistical data analysis, design, and information flow and developed database objects, including tables, views and materialized views using SQL.

NVIDIA Artificial Intelligence Researcher December 2018 - January 2019 (2 months)

Noida Area, India

Use machine learning techniques to perform prediction/regression tasks as required by the problem statement and hyper-parameters in order to achieve the best performance as per the defined goal

IBM

Data Miner

June 2018 - June 2018 (1 month)

Chennai Area, India

Determine processes for centralizing collected data from numerous databases and to design data analysis services to mine for business process information

Education

SRM University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Daffodils Public School

· (2005 - 2016)